Guide to the Office of Administration and Facilities, Eileen Buckley 1959-1995 (Bulk 1964-1989) RG 8.0 RG 8.0
New York University Archives
Records of the Office of Administration and Facilities (Eileen Buckley)
Bulk, 1964-1989
1959-1995, (Bulk 1964-1989)
RG 8.0
New York University Archives
22.0 linear feet 22 linear feet (44 boxes)
The Records of the Office of Administration and Faciliites, Eileen Buckley contain a wide array of information related to the University's property holdings. Included in the collection are materials that document real estate transactions, plans for future development, and maintence of institutional facilities. The collection spans from 1959-1995.
New York University. Office of Administration and Facilities.
Arrangement
Folders are arranged alphabetically by subject heading then chronologically within each subject heading.
The files are grouped into one series:
I, General Files
Physical Access
Please note that this collection is stored offsite, and you must contact the repository to schedule access.
Separated Material
There is no information about materials that are associated by provenance to the described materials that have been physically separated or removed.
Scope and Content Note
The collection consists of financial records, correspondence, project development plans that outline the University's insitutional facilities and its plans for future development. Also included in the collection are contracts between the University and construction companies, budgets for current and future expansion, and reports on the physical condition of NYU buildings.
Historical/Biographical Note
Eileen Buckley worked for the Office of Administration and Facilities.
Access Restrictions
Institutional records of New York University are closed for a period of 20 years from the date of their creation (the date on which each document was written). Board of Trustees records are similarly closed for 35 years from the date of creation. The opening date for files spanning several years will be 20 years from the most recent date. Access will be given to material already 20 years old contained within a collection that is not yet open when such material can be isolated from the rest of the collection.
Materials related to personnel, faculty grievances, job searches and all files included in the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA) are permanently restricted.
Provenance
Administrative transfer in 2004.
New York University.; Budgets.; Clippings (information artifacts); Contracts.; Correspondence.; Financial records.; New York (State) |z New York.; New York University |x Administration.; New York University |x Buildings.
- Series I: General Files
  - Administrative and Professional Classification Program Report, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    General note
    barcode: 3 1142 04058428 9
  - Administrative Reorganization, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Aerospace-Relocation to Barney Building, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Aerospace - Relocation to Long Island, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - AIDS: Projects in Other Universities, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - AIDS: Publications, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Air Pollution Controls/Ovitron Proposal, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Albany Day, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Albany Day Briefing/Book, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Albright, Robert, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Alcohol Policies, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - All University Convocation, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Altieri, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - American Jewish Congress, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - American Jewish Congress, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - American Noble Archives, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - American Universities of Paris, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Anatomy of Hate, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Andreotti, Giulio His Excellency (Special Academic Convocation) 1990, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Andrews Avenue 2190, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Andrews Avenue 2202, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Andrews Avenue 2209, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Andrews Avenue 2211/Kappa Sigma Frat, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Andrews Avenue 2215, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Angelopoulos, Angelos, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Annenberg/CPB Project, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Annenberg/CPB Project, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Annual Appointments, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Annual Reports, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Appleby, Anita, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Appleby, Lee, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Arbator, Georgi, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Architect, undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Archivist Program, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Asbestos, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Asbestos - Deferred Maintenance, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Asbestos - General Correspondence, 1, undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Asbestos - General Correspondence, 2, undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Asbestos - Misc., undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Asbestos - Reports, 1, undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Asbestos - Reports, 2, undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Asbestos - Task Force, undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Asian Studies, undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Association of Black Faculty and Administration (ABFA), undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Association for Education in Journalism and Mass Communications (AEJMC), undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Association of American Colleges, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Association of American Colleges, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Association of Governing Boards of Universities and Colleges, undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Association of Urban Universities, undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Austin, Campbell, undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Avitabile, Richard, undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Bacon, Arthur L., 1991 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058429 7
  - Baer, Norbert S., 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Bahl, Binay, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Bakal, Marcy B., 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - BA/MD Program, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Barbados, Joseph, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Barbera, Alfonso, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Barney Building, 1987
  - Barrios, Eris, 1980-1983 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Basic Science, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Basic Science Relocation, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Battery Park City, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Baudoin, Phyllis A., 1991 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Bayrd Still Fellowship (1988 - 1989) (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Beekman School - African Studies Program, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Begun, Martin, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Beliard, Jean (1988) (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Bell, Jordy, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Bellevue Area Redevelopment Program, 1960
  - Bellevue Area Cooperative Care, 1963-1965 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Bellevue Cooperative Care - 1, 1961-1972 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Bellevue Cooperative Care - 2, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Bellevue - Misc., 1985 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Bellevue Psychiatric Building Site, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Bellevue South - NYR 18 Amended Urban Renewal Plan (1 of 2), 1967-1977 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Bellevue South - NYR 18 Amended Urban Renewal Plan (2 of 2), 1967-1977 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Bellevue South - Disposition Agreement, 1978-1982 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Bellevue South - Parcels 13A and 13B, 1971-1977 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Bellevue South - Development Parcels 13A and 13B Disposition Agreements (2), 1968-1970 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Bellevue South - Development Parcels 13A and 13B Disposition Agreements (4), 1972 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Bellevue South Parcels 13A and 13B Deeds (Closing), 1965-1983
  - Bellevue South - Redevelopement, Misc. Correspondence, 1956-1985 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Bellevue South - Redevelopement Parcels 13A and 13B Disposition Agreements (1), 1965-1968 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Bellevue South - Redevelopment Parcels 13A and 13B Disposition Agreements (3), 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - NYU Medical Center Support Services Building Application, 1979
  - Bender, Thomas, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Benefits, 1989-1993 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Benjamin Franklin National Memorial Awards, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Berkman, Herman, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Berlin - New York, 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Berlowitz, Leslie, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Berlowitz - Personal Notes, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Bernstein, Richard A, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Bess, James L, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Beth Israel Methadone Clinic, 1986
  - Bicentennial Social Studies Fair, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Bing, Richard, undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Biochemistry, 1980-1987 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Biomagnetism Conference 14-18 August, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Bishop, Thomas, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Bjerkebek, Catharine, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Black History Month, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Blacks in Higher Education, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058430 5
  - Black Rock Forest, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Black Rock Forest, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Black Rock Forest, 1990-1992 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Black Rock Forest, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Black Rock Forest, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Bleeker Street 77, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Blueprints - Misc., undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Bly, William, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Board Memberships, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Board of Education, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Board of Estimate, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Board of Estimate - Transcript of Meeting, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Board of Standards and Appeals - Transcript of Hearings, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Board of Trustees, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Board of Trustees, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Board of Trustees, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Board of Trustees, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Board of Trustees, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Board of Trustees - Academic Affairs Committee, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Board of Trustees - Academic Affairs Committee, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Board of Trustees, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058431 3
  - Board of Trustees- Agendas, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees- Buildings and Grounds Committee Correspondence, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees- Minutes, 1960-1962 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees- Minutes, 1962-1965 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Bobst Library Exhibit- Greenwich Village, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Bobst Literary Awards, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Bobst Renovation, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Bobst Security, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Bomb Threat Procedure, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Bonifield, William C., undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Boone, Harry, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Borelle, Gerald, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Boston University - University Professors Program, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Botez, Dr. Nihi C. - Guest Scholar Wilson Center, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Bozkar, Volcan, undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Brademas, John, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Brademas - Speeches and Reports, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Bradley, Karen, undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Bragg, Sadie C., undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Briarcliff College, undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Bridgford, Kim, undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Briggs, Charles, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058432 1
  - Broadway - 65, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Broadway - 311-321 West, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Broadway - 599, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Broadway - 611, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Broadway - 611-621, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Broadway - 656, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Broadway - 679, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Broadway - 684, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Broadway - 692, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Broadway - 692 (Condo Agreement), undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Broadway - 693, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Broadway - 694 (Condo Purchase), undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Broadway - 700, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Broadway - 703-705, undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Broadway - 711-713, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Broadway - 712-716, undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Broadway - 787-789, undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Broadway - 1369-1377 Brooklyn, undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Bromley, Dr. D. Allen, undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Brown, Roscoe, undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Budget, undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Budget, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Budget, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058433 9
  - Budget, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Budget, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Budget, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Budget, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Budget, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Budget - Capital Budget, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Budget - Capital Projects, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Budget - Capital Projects Pending Approval, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Budget - Classrooms, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Budget - Deans Review, undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Budget - Energy File, undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Budget - Institutional Facilites Division, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Budget - Items Pending, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Budget - Operating Budget, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058434 7
  - Budget - Operating Budget, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Budget - Operating Budget, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Budget - Operating Budget, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Budget - Plant Budget Real Estate, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Budget - Protection Department, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Budget - Real Estate, 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Budget - Real Estate, 1984-1984 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Budget - Real Estate, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Budget - Residence Halls, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Budget - Students, undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Budget - VP of Administration, undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Bukay, David - University of Haifa, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Burbank, Ellen, undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Burlingame, Lloyd, undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Burton, Ann, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Cahill, Kevin, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058435 4
  - Calbert, Roosevelt, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Calandra, Regina - Telecommunications, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Calvo, John, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Camey, George, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Campus Compact, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Canadian Property (Henry Heart Rice), undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Cannon, Rosalie, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Cantor, Norman, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Capetown Project, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Capital Items - $500,000 Projects Applied, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Capital Needs, undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Cappell, Sylvain E., undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Carey, Patricia, undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Carlisle, undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Carnegie Commission on Science, Technology, undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Carron, Ann, undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - CAS, undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Casa Hispanica, undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - CASE - Professor of the Year, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Castillo Cultural Center, undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Catering, undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Cedar Avenue -2170, undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Celtic Studies, undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Center for Celtic Studies - NYU Proposal, undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Center for Migration Studies - Quincentennial, undated (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Center for Safety, undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Central Chilling Plant, undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Central Heating Plant Operation, 1961-1971 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Central Refrigeration Plant - Tisch Hall, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Century Club, undated (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Chan, Ken, undated (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Chan, Steven House, 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Chancellor's Scholarship Competition, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Chanin, Lynne S., undated (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Charles A. Dana Award, undated (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Charles, Bernanrd, undated (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Chaudhuri, Una, undated (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Chemistry Building, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Cheney, Lynne, undated (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Cherry, Wilsonia, undated (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Chief Academic Officer Exhibit, undated (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Child Care, undated (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Childrens Express, undated (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Chinchar, Giovina, undated (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Christmas Cards, undated (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Christopher Street - 114, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Chronological, undated (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Chronological - Documents, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Chronological - File, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058436 2
  - Cipolla, Carlo, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - City University New York - Board of Trustees Taskforce, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - City University New York - Center for Minorities, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Clark, F. Thomas, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Claxton, Allen, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Coates, Tony, undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Cogeneration, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Cogeneration - Environmental Clearances, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Cogeneration/Power Problems, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Cohen, Eli, undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Cohen, Norman, undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Cole, Johnetta, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Coleman, Kevin, undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Coles, Leonard S., undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Coles - Budget Meetings, undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Coles - Community Board 2, undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Coles - Managament Review Group, undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Coles - Planning and Construction, undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Coles - Pool, Bleachers, Equipment, and Courts, undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Coles - Recreation Center, 1974-1978 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Coles - Zoning, Land, Architecture, undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Collaborative Newsletter, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058437 0
  - The College Board, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Collins, Tim, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Columbo, Furio, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Commencement, 1990-1993 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Commission on International Community, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Academic Quality, undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Committee of Vice Chancellors and Principals of the UK, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Community Board 2, undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Community Board 2 - Resource Directory, undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Community College Transfer, undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Community Fund, undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Community Relations, undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Community of Scholars, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Community Service, undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Community Service Grants, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Comprehensive Region Center for the Humanities - CRCH, undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Computer Information, undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Conference on Collaboration, undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Conference Report, undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Conflict of Interest, undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Congress of Racial Equality, undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Consortium of Humanity Center and Institutes - CHCI, undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Consortium of Social Science Association, undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Contracts: A.J. Lanzo Lab, undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Contracts: Arts and Science Capital Improvement Project, undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library, undated (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library, undated (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library, undated (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library, undated (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library - Bidders, undated (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library - Board of Standards and Appeals, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library - Board of Standards and Appeals, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library - Board of Standards and Appeals, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library - Board of Trustees Actions, undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058438 8
  - Contracts: Bobst Library - Budgets and Costs, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library - Carpeting Study, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library - Change Orders, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library - Computer Center, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library - Construction, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library - Construction Fees, 1963-1965 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library - Construction Fees, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library - Construction Fees, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library - Dedication, undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library - Diesel Claims, undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library - Driscoll Company/Delays and Claims, undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library - Driscoll Company/Stone Delivery, undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library - Driscoll Company/Termination of Construction, undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library - Easement and Franchise Agreeement, undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library - Facilities Planning, 1959-1963 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library - Financing/Dormitory Authority, undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library - Financing/H.E.F.A.-Title III, undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library - Furnishings, undated (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library - General Correspondence, undated (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library - General Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library - Insurance, undated (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library - Lawsuit/Driscoll/Bonding Company, undated (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library - McCormick Company, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058439 6
  - Contracts: Bobst Library - Operation Budget, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library - Planning, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library - Planning and Design Correspondence, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library - Planning and Design/Consult, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library - Plaza, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library - Progress, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library - Quarry Agreement, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library - Quarry Agreement - Talcott, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library - Quarry Agreement/Driscoll and McCormick, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library - Sandstone, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library - Security, undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library - Site, undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library - Twelfth Floor, undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Contracts: Bobst Library - Virgil Thompson Room, undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Contracts: Coles - Newspaper Clippings, undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Contracts: Coles - Recreation Budget, undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Contracts: Dental Center - Basic Science Maps, undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Contracts: Dental Center - Capital Budget, undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Contracts: Dental Center - Education/Facility/Construction, undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Contracts: Dental Center - Facility Dental Health Services, undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Contracts: Dental Center - Ocuupancy, undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Contracts: Dental Center - Purchasing, undated (Box 12, Folder 23)